<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://qwdio.top</id>
    <title>希望之洋</title>
    <updated>2025-03-13T09:27:24.801Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://qwdio.top"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://qwdio.top/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>自信即巅峰</subtitle>
    <logo>https://qwdio.top/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://qwdio.top/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2025, 希望之洋</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSE]]></title>
        <id>https://qwdio.top/GPER6EuRqD/</id>
        <link href="https://qwdio.top/GPER6EuRqD/">
        </link>
        <updated>2025-03-13T07:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Background Story for HKDSE 2025 English Speaking Exam</strong></p>
<p>In 2025, Hong Kong unveiled its <strong>Kai Tak Sports Park</strong>, a landmark project transforming the former airport site into Asia’s premier sports and entertainment hub. The park, featuring a 50,000-seat retractable-roof stadium and cutting-edge facilities, hosted its inaugural event—the Hong Kong Sevens Rugby Tournament—amidst global anticipation. While citizens marveled at the AI-powered crowd management system and futuristic design, critics questioned operational readiness and maintenance costs. Meanwhile, teens flocked to the park’s retail zone, snapping selfies against the Victoria Harbour skyline, as vendors in nearby Kowloon City adapted their stalls to cater to international tourists.</p>
<hr>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://qwdio.top/post-images/1741858035161.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<hr>
<h4 id="part-a-group-interaction"><strong>PART A Group Interaction</strong></h4>
<p><strong>Discuss:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Economic and cultural impact of Kai Tak Sports Park on Hong Kong</li>
<li>Challenges in maintaining large-scale sports infrastructure</li>
<li>Whether Hong Kong is prepared to host global mega-events</li>
<li>Any other critical factors</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h4 id="part-b-individual-response"><strong>PART B Individual Response</strong></h4>
<ol>
<li>Have you visited Kai Tak Sports Park? Share your experience.</li>
<li>How might the park influence youth participation in sports?</li>
<li>Would you pay higher taxes to fund similar projects?</li>
<li>How effective are public transport links to the park?</li>
<li>Could traditional neighborhoods coexist with the park’s modern development?</li>
<li>Is Hong Kong’s sports infrastructure superior to other Asian cities?</li>
<li>Should the government prioritize sports or housing investments?</li>
<li>Will the park significantly boost Hong Kong’s international image?</li>
</ol>
<hr>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>